starsdiettips.com 2016-01-23

# Privacy Policy | Diets

Celebritydietrules (“Celebritydietrules “) is committed to protecting its users’ privacy. This Privacy Policy (the “Privacy Policy”), as set forth below, covers Celebritydietrules .com (“Celebritydietrules .com,” the “Site,” or the “website”) and applies solely to information collected on Celebritydietrules .com . Please read this Privacy Policy to understand how we will treat personally and non-personally identifiable information we collect on Celebritydietrules .com. This Privacy Policy may change from time to time, so please check back periodically.

**_What non-personally identifiable information is collected automatically?_**

We automatically collect certain non-personally identifiable information from you to optimize our web pages for your computer such as:

  * clickstream information (internet protocol (“IP”) address, internet service provider, platform type, date/time stamp) http protocol information (last URL requested and browser type)
  * interaction information (browser interaction such as when the mouse moves over an image)
  * computer information (computer and browser information)
  * search terms (search text)

We may use such non-personally identifiable information for internal purposes, including, but not limited to, improving the content of the Site and the services offered on the Site. (See “How is my information used?”)

**_How is my information used?_**

We will use personally identifiable information that you submit to the Site for the purposes for which you submitted it. At the time you provide personally identifiable information, you have the option of instructing us not to send you our special email offers, and of affirmatively consenting to receiving email offers about, or from, our partners.

We may disclose personally identifiable information when required by law or when we have a good faith belief that such action is necessary to comply with a current judicial proceeding, court order, government investigation or legal process. We may, in our sole discretion, comply with subpoenas seeking personal information without notifying you.

We may use non-personally identifiable information collected on the Site to enhance the Site and our product offerings, to maintain and secure the Site, and to understand the interests of Site visitors. Generally, we use non-personally identifiable information to analyze trends, administer the website, and gather information for aggregate use (IP addresses are not linked to personally identifiable information).

We may also use the statistical compilation and aggregation of non-personally identifiable information and may provide such information to third parties for marketing, advertising or research purposes.

We may also disclose your personally identifiable information to any third party as we, in our sole discretion, believe necessary or appropriate, in connection with a merger or consolidation with such third party or the sale of some or all of our assets, provided that such third party agrees to comply with the then-current version of this Privacy Policy.

**_How is my information kept secure?_**

We maintain commercially reasonable safeguards to ensure the security, integrity and privacy of personally identifiable information submitted to our Sites, and we periodically review and update security measures in light of current technologies. However, you should be aware that security measures sometimes fail, and we make no guarantees regarding the security of your personally identifiable information.

**_What are cookies and how are they used by the Sites?_**

Cookies are files that a web site places on an individual’s hard-drive for record-keeping purposes. Cookies, which are an industry standard used by most web sites, can facilitate a user’s ongoing access to and use of a site.

Our cookies cannot be used to run programs or deliver viruses to your computer. Cookies are uniquely assigned to you, and can only be read by a web server in the domain that issued the cookie to you. We will not share or sell non-aggregated information contained within cookies with any third party. The cookie itself does not contain any personally identifiable information.

If you do not want information collected through the use of cookies, there is a simple procedure in most browsers that allows you to deny or accept the cookie feature, but you should note that cookies may be necessary to provide you with such special features as customized content delivery. Cookies can be removed from your computer by following Internet browser “help” file directions.

**_What do I need to know about third party sites, co-branded sites, and Celebritydietrules ‘s online business partners?_**

We have established relationships that allow visitors to the Site to go directly to sites operated by third parties. Some of these sites may be co-branded with our logos; however, they are not operated or maintained by Celebritydietrules . We are not responsible for the content or practices of web sites operated by third parties that are linked to the Site. These links are meant for the user’s convenience only. Links to third party sites do not constitute our sponsorship, endorsement or approval of the content, policies or practices of such third party sites. Once you have left the Site via such a link, you should check the applicable privacy policy of the third party site.

We may use third parties to manage sweepstakes, games, contests, chats or other features, and these parties may have access to personally identifiable information submitted by visitors who participate in those activities.

**_Does Celebritydietrules use Third Party Ad Servers?_**

We use third party advertising companies and advertising networks to deliver advertisements on the Site. These companies may use cookies, web beacons, clear .gifs or similar technologies to help present such advertisements, and to help measure and research the advertisements’ effectiveness. The use of these technologies by these companies is subject to their own privacy policies and is not covered by this Privacy Policy. If you would like more information about this practice please visit www.networkadvertising.org.

**_Does Celebritydietrules collect personally identifiable information from children?_**

We ask that all parents spend time with their children and monitor what sites their children are visiting. We do not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from children under the age of 13. We also suggest that no children under 18 submit personally identifiable information to any game, membership, contest or promotion that we might host without first obtaining a parent’s consent. Our Site is not intended for use by and is not directed to children.

**_Changes to this Privacy Policy_**

We will occasionally update this Privacy Policy. When we do, we will also revise the “last updated” date at the bottom of the Privacy Policy. For material changes to this Privacy Policy, we will notify you by placing a prominent notice on the Site.
